

SEMO, Cape Girardeau
1 (217) 891-6943
adamwproductions@gmail.com
adamweatherby.dev

WHO AM I?

Hello, I am Adam Weatherby. I am currently a student at Southeast Missouri University. I am pursuing a career in software development. I am a member of the Computer Science Club and I work on campus doing research for the CS department. I enjoy watching/making movies with my friends, as well as playing video games.

EXPERIENCE

5/2020 - 9/2020 **Research Assistant**

SEMO CS Department

- Assist Grad students and Professors conduct research projects and write papers.
- Design methodologies for gathering various metrics from different software and hardware configurations.
- Assist associates with installations, configurations, troubleshooting, and problem solving.
- Set up remote Linux servers for others to access while working from home.

8/2019 - Present Student Caller

SEMO Annual Fund

- Work with supervisors and team members to set earnings goals and make plans on how to reach them.
- Call SEMO alumni to update their contact information and help keep them active as alumni.
- Participate in team building exercises as well as cooperative efforts with fellow Annual Fund employees.

8/2017 – 10/2017 **Lab Assistant**

PH Broughton

- Set up and operate test equipment to evaluate performance of developmental parts, assemblies, or systems under simulated operating conditions, and record results.
- Conduct inspections for quality control and assurance programs, reporting findings and recommendations
- Analyze and interpret test information to resolve design-related problems.
- Compile and interpret results of tests and analyses.

EDUCATION

2018 - Present B.S. Computer Science

SOUTHEAST MISSOURI STATE UNIVERSITY

- Institutional GPA: 3.41
- Extracurricular Activity: Computer Science Club
- Relevant Course: Computer Science 1, Computer Science 2, Computer Science 3, Database, Cybersecurity, Discrete mathematics, C and the Posix environment, and miscellaneous IT courses.

PROJECTS

Data Visualizer - Project to visualize Linked Lists, Stacks, and Queues using HTML/JavaScript

Multi-threaded CSV Generator/Sorter - Project for generating 1000 random numbers. They are written to a CSV file. Then in 4 separate threads they are sorted using Selection sort, Bubble sort, Merge sort, and Quick sort respectively. Written in Java

Maze Game - Simple Maze game written in C

LINK TO PROJECTS

Where you can find links to all the listed programs

